Guide to the William Rufus Shafter Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series VII - Printed Reference
  - Copies (Box 8, Folder 80)
Wompatuck (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
Wood, Leonard Brig. Gen., Surg. Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 57
Word, Marshall W. Maj. Surg. Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 39
Wood, W. Clay Maj. Roll I Folder 1
Woodruf, Thomas H. Maj. Roll II Folder 12 Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll VI Folder 51
Worden, Charles A. Capt. Roll IV Folder 35
The World (New York Newspaper) Roll V Folder 45
Worth, William S. Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 27
Wounded Knee Roll I Folder 8
Wright, Samuel Capt., 1777 Roll I Folder 8
Wright, Thomas T. Roll VI Folder 52
Wright, William M. Capt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 37
Yale (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 25, Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44
Yellow Fever Roll I Folder 9 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 57
Yellow Press Roll VI Folder 50
Yermoloff, [?] Col., Military Attache, Russia Roll VI Folder 52
Yorktown, Siege of Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 57
Yosemite (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16
Young, Clarence Roll V Folder 48
Young, Samuel B. M. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 6, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 35 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 57
Young, William H. Roll I Folder 8
Yslisesel, Don Luis Maj., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 26
Yucatan (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 23 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 52
Zaza, Cuba Roll I Folder 9
Zertrichi, [?] Maj., Mex. Forces Roll I Folder 5, Folder 6
Zuaga, Juan Roll I Folder 5